<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>3D geospatial vision</title>
    <description>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.
</description>
    <link>https://yweirt.github.io/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://yweirt.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2019 17:17:57 +0800</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2019 17:17:57 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.0.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Multimodal aerial data set for line-based co-registration has been released</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Yao, Wei; Polewski, Przemyslaw (2018), “Multimodal aerial data for line-based co-registration”, Mendeley Data, v2, http://dx.doi.org/10.17632/dmp7tkn8kc.2. &lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.17632/dmp7tkn8kc.2&quot;&gt;Details can be referred to that page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You are welcome to adopt above-mentioned dataset for verifying and testing your own developed algorithms with respect to Line-based coregistration and report the comparison with our baseline results by citing following paper:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Polewski, P., &amp;amp; Yao, W. (2019). Scale invariant line-based co-registration of multimodal aerial data using L1 minimization of spatial and angular deviations. ISPRS Journal of Photogrammetry and Remote Sensing, 152, 79-93. &lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.isprsjprs.2019.04.004&quot;&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2019 09:20:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>https://yweirt.github.io/news/2019/06/15/MM-Data-Line-Intergration.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://yweirt.github.io/news/2019/06/15/MM-Data-Line-Intergration.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>news</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Call for paper @ Point Cloud Processing in Remote Sensing </title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;You are welcome to submit contributions to Special Issue “Point Cloud Processing in Remote Sensing”, which is a special issue of Remote Sensing (ISSN 2072-4292). This special issue belongs to the section “Remote Sensing Image Processing”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Deadline for manuscript submissions: 31 March 2020, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mdpi.com/journal/remotesensing/special_issues/Point_Cloud_RS&quot;&gt;Details can be referred to that page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 15:55:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>https://yweirt.github.io/news/2019/02/12/RS-SI.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://yweirt.github.io/news/2019/02/12/RS-SI.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>news</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Our LiDAR based regeneration mapping paper has won the ITC Publication Award</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The annual ITC Publication Award was given to Nina Amiri for the paper &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0303243416301052&quot;&gt;Estimation of regeneration coverage in a temperate forest by 3D segmentation using airborne laser scanning data&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nina is jointly supervised as a PhD student at the Munich University of Applied Sciences and the University of Twente. In the study, a comparison between ground plot data, with three airborne LiDAR images collected between 2009 and 2012, showed that the actual and estimated area of regeneration, agreed with a 70% accuracy. Further, as the amount of canopy cover increased the accuracy mapping forest regeneration decreased. In addition, regenerating forests were more accurately mapped under conifer overstory than deciduous overstory, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.itc.nl/Pub/News-overview/2017/in2017-september/Opening-of-the-Academic-Programme-2017-2018.html&quot;&gt;details are available on that page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Congratulations to Nina!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 09:35:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>https://yweirt.github.io/news/2017/11/13/ITCaward.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://yweirt.github.io/news/2017/11/13/ITCaward.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>news</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New PhD research assistants/Postdoctoral fellow: positions available in intelligent manipulation of multimodality 3D point clouds and images of both urban and natural enviroment</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We are looking for new PhD students/research assistants and postdoctoral research fellows to join our group. 
The project is in collaboration with the German/Chinese company/research institutions including &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.3d.de&quot;&gt;3D Mapping&lt;/a&gt; and different partners around the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Deadline to apply is 2017-11-15, and &lt;a href=&quot;/jobs/phdrs2017/Letterhead_LSGI_int.pdf&quot;&gt;all details are available on that page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://player.vimeo.com/video/146221307?color=ff9933&quot; width=&quot;640&quot; height=&quot;360&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; webkitallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; mozallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://vimeo.com/146221307&quot;&gt;3D - Geoworld&lt;/a&gt; from &lt;a href=&quot;https://vimeo.com/cyclomedia&quot;&gt;CycloMedia&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&quot;https://vimeo.com&quot;&gt;Vimeo&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 08:57:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>https://yweirt.github.io/news/2017/08/17/phd-position.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://yweirt.github.io/news/2017/08/17/phd-position.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>news</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Workshops at ISPRS Geospatial Week 2017 on Laser scanning and Data fusion</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;On 18-20 September 2017 we have organised &lt;a href=&quot;http://www2.ipf.kit.edu/laserscanning2017/&quot;&gt;two workshops on Laser scanning and Data fusion&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The aim of the workshop was to bring experts on laser scanning and 3D remote sensing for urban and geospatial applications together and explore potential collaborations. The workshop is organised in relation to the &lt;a href=&quot;http://gsw2017.3snews.net/index.php?siteid=2&quot;&gt;ISPRS Geospatial Week 2017 (GSW2017)&lt;/a&gt;, and it involved presentations from academia, industry, and government.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://gsw2017.3snews.net/index.php?siteid=2&quot;&gt;GSW2017&lt;/a&gt; is an talent is educated and engineers, designers, digital engineers and natural/social scientists jointly develop and valorise interdisciplinary metropolitan solutions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/2017/ams-.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/img/2017/ams-1.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/img/2017/am.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2017 08:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>https://yweirt.github.io/news/2017/08/15/ISPRS-workshop.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://yweirt.github.io/news/2017/08/15/ISPRS-workshop.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>news</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hello 3D geospatial world</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Since 1st of August 2017, our 3D geospatial vision group has started.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3D geoinformation and computer vision methodology are extremely important to manage, predict and interpret the complex reality. We study and develop multil-modality remote sensing techniques to acquire, extract, analyse and model 3D geoinformation. We develop solutions in close collaboration with users such as experts of forestry, smart city, disaster mitigation and ecological modelling. Our group is located within the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.lsgi.polyu.edu.hk/home/index.asp&quot;&gt;Department of Land Surveying and Geo-Informatics&lt;/a&gt;, since 3D is a key aspect in the design and analysis of interactions in the urban and natual environment. We are therefore very close to the main users of urban and enviromental informatics who can advance in their own domain by using ours and vice versa.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our group consists of one faculty member and  with different but completing expertise in the domain of 3D modeling: &lt;a href=&quot;https://yweirt.github.io&quot;&gt;Wei Yao&lt;/a&gt; (3D geospatial vision and intelligence), and several PhD students and research scientists/visitors permanently work on highly relevant topics as you can see on our &lt;a href=&quot;/about&quot;&gt;staff&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;/projects&quot;&gt;projects&lt;/a&gt; pages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are looking forward to develop and provide solutions for a solid and sustainable 3D data and technical basis to support existing and new applications!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>https://yweirt.github.io/news/2017/08/05/hello-3d-world.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://yweirt.github.io/news/2017/08/05/hello-3d-world.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>news</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
